[
  {
    "question": "A Controller is a class file that can be associated with a URI.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is a class file that can be associated with a URI.",
    "choices": [
      "Function",
      "Control",
      "Controller"
    ],
    "answer": "Controller"
  },
  {
    "question": "______ is an Application Development Framework - a toolkit - for people who build web sites using PHP.",
    "choices": [
      "Wordpress",
      "CodeIgniter",
      "Joomla",
      "Zend"
    ],
    "answer": "CodeIgniter"
  },
  {
    "question": "List features of CodeIgniter.",
    "choices": [
      "All of these",
      "Model View Controller support System",
      "Full featured database classes with compatibility to several platforms",
      "Extremely Light Weight"
    ],
    "answer": "All of these"
  },
  {
    "question": "Controllers are the heart of your application, as they determine how HTTP requests should be handled.",
    "choices": [
      "False",
      "True"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Views are called directly and must be loaded by a controller.",
    "choices": [
      "False",
      "True"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The .php file extension does not need to be specified unless you use something other than .php.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "CodeIgniter will intelligently handle multiple calls to $this->load->view() from within a controller.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "CodeIgniter will handle multiple calls to $this->load->view() from within a controller.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "To load a view file you will use the following method:",
    "choices": [
      "$this->load->file('name')",
      "$this->load->view('name')",
      "$this->load->data('name')"
    ],
    "answer": "$this->load->view('name')"
  },
  {
    "question": "CodeIgniter can load a default controller if only your site root URL is requested",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "In this example: example.com/class/function/ID/foo/bar, what is the controller class?",
    "choices": [
      "class",
      "example.com",
      "function"
    ],
    "answer": "class"
  },
  {
    "question": "In an MVC framework, the Controller acts as the orchestrator, so it is responsible for fetching a particular view.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "An example of storing view within sub-directories: $this->view('subdirectory_name/file_name');",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "A view is simply a web page, or a page fragment (header, footer) and can be embedded within other views.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Views are called directly and must be loaded by a controller.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the example: example.com/index.php/blog/, the , Codelgniter would attempt to?",
    "choices": [
      "Call a function blog",
      "Find a controller named Blog.php",
      "Create a class blog"
    ],
    "answer": "Find a controller named Blog.php"
  },
  {
    "question": "An example of storing view within sub-directories: $this->load->view('directory_name/file_name');",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The application/config/routes.php file determines which controller is called by default",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "This has an invalid class name: <?php class blog extends CI_Controller { }",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Data is passed from the controller to the view by way of an array in the second parameter of the view loading method.",
    "choices": [
      "False",
      "True"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Views are never called directly; they must be loaded by a controller.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Controller should extends the parent controller class so that it can inherit all its methods.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "If your URI contains more than two segments they will be passed to your method as function",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  }
]